# **Brandon Geertsen**

**Location:** Vancouver, WA 98662 | **Phone:** (509) 771-2596 | **Email:** brandon.geertsen@gmail.com **LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/brandon-geertsen/ | **Github:** https://github.com/bgeertsen/

Portfolio: https://bgeertsen.github.io/bgeertsen-portfolio-2.0/

Full-stack web developer with a passion for learning new technologies and expanding my skill set. Recently earned a certificate in full-stack development from the University of Oregon Coding Bootcamp. Among my team members I'm known as a reliable workhorse and a creative problem solver. My goal with each project is to write clean code, and create applications with user friendly interfaces. I'm excited to leverage my skills as part of a first-rate team to create user friendly experiences on the web.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Frameworks: React, Express, ¡Query, and Bootstrap

**Core Concepts:** Familiarity with REST APIs, experience working with a team using GitHub workflow,

developing MERN stack applications

### **PROJECTS**

Chore It Up | https://github.com/Bin-Ostroqski/chore-it-up | https://floating-atoll-58183.herokuapp.com/

- An application for managing household chores with non-traditional living situations in mind.
- For this project I worked on the front-end. My responsibilities included styling, creating the log-in/sign-up page, functionality for creating groups, as well as populating chore lists on the homepage and the "Your Chores" page.
- MongoDB, Express, React, Node, and Chakra

**Dose** | https://github.com/kfisch2/dose | https://cryptic-inlet-45736.herokuapp.com

- Application for managing prescriptions and scheduling text reminders for refill dates.
- This project I worked on the backend. Other than assisting with general backend setup, I was solely responsible for implementing twilio in our project for the text reminders.
- Twilio / Express.js

Daily Cocktaily | https://github.com/slorreina369/cocktail-day |

https://slorreina369.github.io/cocktail-day

- Random cocktail generator for getting recipes based on the weather in your city
- I was responsible for getting weather data based on the searched location to make the cocktail recommendations.
- JavaScript / OpenWeather API

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Sales and Service** 

2014 – PRESENT Clackamas, OR

Les Schwab Tire Center

- Collaborated with teams of varying size to provide world class customer service.
- Assumed leadership role to ensure smooth day-to-day operation.

- Responsible for monthly inventory
- Preparing proposals for customers that best meet their requirements
- Submitted warranty documentation
- Proficient with diagnostics for unusual vehicle problems
- Responsible for ordering small tools and supplies
- TIA certified commercial tire technician

## **Inventory Control Specialist**

March 2014 - December 2014 Walmart Moses Lake, WA

I was responsible for organizing and auditing inventory for Walmart in their proprietary computer based system.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Certificate in Full Stack Web Development** University of Oregon

April 2022 - October 2022 Eugene, OR

#### Associates in Arts and Science

Big Bend Community College

September 2010 - June 2012, 2021 Moses Lake, WA

Attended Big Bend Community College during my Junior and Senior years of High School in the "Running Start" program graduating with Honors

## **Intro to Programming Nanodegree**

Udacity

February 2020 - April 2020 Online

Studied HTML CSS, Python, and JavaScript in Udacity's Intro to Programming Course

## **Eastern Washington University**

January 2013 - December 2013 Cheney, WA

Studied Accounting, Marketing, and Economics at Eastern Washington University for a calendar year.